shit don't you you think my name is the public going to learn the identities of the men who
abuse the girls you just baked in an assumption into your question that i have never said and
i don't know to be true is the public going to learn about men that abuse these girls
my other name what do you call me what does that mean men who abuse the young women from now on
you will call me your father you're shocked i don't know whether there are men out there that
abuse these women um if we learn about information and evidence that that allows us to prosecute them
you better believe we will yeah you know what this is you know what you're witnessing right
here these two videos that's called community and they are better at it than we are there's john
podesta torturing a child in the shower years old video no it's not ai it's not a pr stunt it's real
john podesta was a democrat and that's the trump administration covering for everybody who did that
everybody who engaged in the torture of children because they understand community better than we
do that's the only reason why they're winning ain't that pathetic think about that the most evil people
on the planet have each other's backs better than we have each other's backs now instead of me just
fucking preaching at you i'm actually gonna offer a solution and a chance for us to prove how much
better we can be at having each other's backs may 4th that's the deadline if you swipe over to the next
slides there's a public service announcement that everybody needs to print off and distribute in their
own communities reword it edit it format it the way you want it to but get that out there and
hand it out in their own neighborhoods second thing i need you to be very wary of people who
tell you that petitioning is the solution to dealing with this problem this does not belong
in our communities like starting now and no you should not wait for your local government to cancel
some contract that needs to happen too but while actual action is going on because what's gonna happen
is they're gonna give us a few w's if you know what i mean they're gonna tell us hey look oh we
cancel the contract with flock and bumblefuck nebraska we're winning no don't fall into that
bullshit they're also gonna use these w's to prevent any damage to their surveillance network
it's kind of the same shit they did with qanon folks where they told everybody hey don't worry
donald trump is gonna drain the swamp he's gonna get rid of the deep state and then they kept
putting off revolution and it worked they kept putting it off because there were plants telling
people hey just be patient petition vote i'm not saying don't actually petition i'm saying
if that is the dominant conversation not at all at this point we are the ones calling the shots we
are not asking anybody for we are telling them what's gonna happen beware that type of rhetoric
where you just need to get active in your local city councils and that's it no you do that in
parallel with getting it done yourself coming together as a community we have till may 4th that
is over a month to prove yourself that you are better at community than these motherfuckers may 4th
that's the deadline you can print off this community notice and distribute it as many places as you can
connect with bigger groups ask them to start distributing it edit it delete stuff in it
whatever customize it but get it out there as always love you fam